{"data":[{"question":"Peter and Mary first met _____ 1982.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Did you go out ______ Monday evening.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Let's meet ______ 8.30 tomorrow evening.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"I'm starting my new job ______ 7 June.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Do you work _____ Saturdays.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":" I got up _____ 8 o'clock this morning.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"My brother got married _____ December.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"George isn't here _____ the moment.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"I often go skiing _____ winter.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"},{"question":"Julia's birthday is ____ November","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"2"}]}